Dominick Reilly

☑ dreilly1@charlotte.edu 😭 dominickrei.github.io 🗘 dominickrei

Research Interests

My current research focuses on video understanding, specifically action recognition for activities of daily living videos taken from monitoring cameras. I would like to become more involved in the challenges of episodic memory from egocentric videos, and also audio-visual representation learning.

Education

University of North Carolina at Charlotte

August 2021 - Present

Doctor of Philosophy, Computer Science

Advisor: Dr. Srijan Das

University of North Carolina at Charlotte

January 2019 - May 2021

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

Overall GPA: 4.0

Experience

University of North Carolina at Charlotte

August 2022 - Present

Research Assistant - Charlotte Machine Learning Lab

- Researching video transformers for understanding activities of daily living videos.
- Researching self-supervised training techniques for image classification with ViTs.

University of North Carolina at Charlotte

July 2021 - July 2022

Research Assistant - Data Privacy Lab

- Researched differentially private approaches to image obfuscation.
- Created a demo demonstrating differentially private image obfuscation. This work was published at EDBT 2022: http://3.223.148.187/.

Publications

- 1. **Dominick Reilly**, Srijan Das, "Just Add π ! Pose Induced Video Transformers for Understanding Activities of Daily Living," arXiv:2311.18840 (Under review), 2024.
- Srijan Das, Tanmay Jain, **Dominick Reilly**, Pranav Balaji, Soumyajit Karmakar, Shyam Marjit, Xiang Li, Abhijit Das, Michael Ryoo, "Limited Data, Unlimited Potential: A Study on ViTs Augmented by Masked Autoencoders," IEEE/CVF Winter Conference on Applications of Computer Vision (WACV), 2024.
- 3. Muhammad Usama Saleem, **Dominick Reilly**, Liyue Fan, "DP-Shield: Face Obfuscation with Differential Privacy," International Conference on Extending Database Technology (EDBT), 2022.
- 4. **Dominick Reilly**, Liyue Fan, "Comparative Evaluation for Differentially Private Image Obfuscation," IEEE International Conference on Trust, Privacy and Security in Intelligent Systems, and Applications (IEEE TPS), 2021.

Academic Activities

• Reviewer at AAAI 2024, AAAI 2023, AI4HC 2023

Awards

- 1. The Chateaubriand Fellowship (awarded by the Embassy of France to U.S. Ph.D. students for conducting research in France), 2023
- $2.\$ Best poster award in Mathematics and Computer Science, UNC Charlotte Undergraduate Research Conference, 2020